daceband.com 2011-05-31

# Daceband - make money sharing videos, blogs, photos and music

Welcome to Daceband. We make it fun and easy for people to make money online. This Privacy Policy describes the method in which Daceband treats and uses personal information that Daceband will receive and collect from you.

### The use of your information

Daceband uses your information solely for the purpose of registering, and to communicate with you as a member of the service.

Daceband will never share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies. 

### Third Party Advertising

Daceband uses third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements in the site. Daceband will never provide these companies your Personal Information, such as gender, age, name, address, email address or any of your information.

### Edit and Delete Your Account Information

Daceband reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the Service, such as service announcements and contest information that are considered part of your Daceband account. If you would like to delete your account, log into Daceband, go to your account page and click on "Cancel my account". 

### Security

We are very concerned about your information and we will try our best to keep it as safe as possible. 

### Other Sites

Daceband allows third party links in our website. Daceband has absolutely no control over and cannot be reliable for their content.

### Under 13

If you are under 13 years of age please do not send us any personal information or even register.

### Contact us

Understand that this privacy policy is not permanent and we may modify it from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your DaceBand account.
